# Elena Hsu-An Experience and **Visual Designer**

www.elenahsu.com yu.elenahsu@gmail.com @mulkfiction

I am passionate in crafting human-centric solutions that interculturally connect human beings to each other.

Adventure-ready, I actively explore new approaches while striving for engaging and effective solutions through design and storytelling.

#### TOOLS







InDesign Illustrator Photoshop



After Effects

Ae

M

Marvel



Sketch







Axure RP

Flinto

Final Cut

#### COMPETENCIES

UX + UI Design **UX Strategy** Visual Design Interaction Design **Brand Identity** Content Strategy HTML/CSS

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Contract Web Designer @SJMA

OCTOBER 2019 - PRESENT

Extending Saint James Music Academy's brand identity into their web presence, I create visual assets for web and development compatible with Keela through WordPress.

#### Designer @RailyardLab @DossierCreative

MAY 2019 - OCTOBER 2019

Railyard Lab is an intern-powered studio within Dossier Creative. Providing hands-on experience, I nurtured my skills in branding, creative strategy, and experience design with local clients within social impact spaces.

### UX Designer @MediaMonksHQ

MAY - AUGUST 2018

Experienced working as a design intern on an international scale. I was responsible for conducting field research, and producing industry-standard wireframes and mockups.

#### Associate Production Editor @ThePeak

DECEMBER 2016 - AUGUST 2017

Within the layout and production department of SFU's student wide newspaper, I coordinated with a team of editorial writers, photographers, and illustrators to deliver captivating full-page layouts for weekly publications in print and digital.

#### **EDUCATION**

## Simon Fraser University

SEPTEMBER 2013 - JUNE 2019

BA. School of Interactive Arts and Technology Concentration in Design

## Malmö University

AUGUST 2017 - JANUARY 2018 Fall Exchange Program K3. Interaction Design Program

Through immersing myself in Scandinavian culture, I enriched my design perspective by learning and applying different approaches. My education specialized in interaction design and tangible and embodied interactions.

LOVES Overweight Cat Videos, Bad Movies, Chicken Broth Ramen